// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
      question: "How can we describe an array in the best possible way?",
    answer: "Container that stores the elements of similar types",
    options: [
      "The Array shows a hierarchical structure.",
      "Arrays are immutable",
      "Container that stores the elements of similar types",
      "The Array is not a data structure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct way of declaring an array?",
    answer: "int javatpoint[10];",
    options: [
      "int javatpoint[10];",
      "int javatpoint;",
      "javatpoint{20};",
      "array javatpoint[10];"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How can we initialize an array in C language?",
    answer: "int arr[2] = {10, 20}",
    options: [
      "int arr[2]=(10, 20)",
      "int arr(2)={10, 20}",
      "int arr[2] = {10, 20}",
      "int arr(2) = (10, 20)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is the advantage of the array data structure?",
    answer: "Easier to access the elements in an array",
    options: [
      "Elements of mixed data types can be stored",
      "Easier to access the elements in an array",
      "Index of the first element starts from 1",
      "Elements of an array cannot be sorted"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following highly uses the concept of an array?",
    answer: "Spatial locality",
    options: [
      "Binary Search tree",
      "Caching",
      "Spatial locality",
      "Scheduling of Processes"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which one of the following is the size of int arr[9] assuming that int is of 4 bytes?",
    answer: "36",
    options: [
      "9",
      "36",
      "35",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which one of the following is the process of inserting an element in the stack?",
    answer: "Push",
    options: [
      "Insert",
      "Add",
      "Push",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When the user tries to delete the element from the empty stack then the condition is said to be a ____",
    answer: "Underflow",
    options: [
      "Underflow",
      "Garbage collection",
      "Overflow",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which one of the following is not the application of the stack data structure.",
    answer: "Asynchronous data transfer",
    options: [
      "String reversal",
      "Recursion",
      "Backtracking",
      "Asynchronous data transfer"
    ]
  },   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which data structure is mainly used for implementing the recursive algorithm?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Queue",
      "Stack",
      "Binary tree",
      "Linked list"
    ]
  },

];